It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
Let's grab hold of our wishes
Translation
FUNimation
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Soundtracking
Halee
Infoboxes/Title Card
BernieCrane
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Editing
Feeso
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Quality Checking
Alasta
Galaxy 9000
Mr. Luffy
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
Timing
Datenshi
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
Combat
It goes in! Goal! Goal! Goal!
All right! Zoro! Sanji! You're awesome!
You bums actually did it!
Y-You did it!
Aww! But I don't wanna give Choppy back!
Zoro! Sanji! Way to go!
Whoa! They're awesome!
Bravo! Bravo!
I'm totally moved to tears!
You guys really are the best!
You dimwits! Who the heck praises their enemy?!
I can't believe this! No one defeats the Groggy Monsters...!
Oh hi Ref. Wakey-wakey.
Hurry and blow the whistle! Go on!
O-Oh right.
His behavior toward me was a flagrant foul!
He's outta the game!
And there's the final whistle!
The Groggy Ring match is over!
Thanks for your hard work!
In Round #2 of the Davy Back Fight,
Team Straw Hat has unbelievably snatched victory away
from the previously undefeated Groggy Monsters!
Of course we won! Zoro and Sanji would never lose!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Did you see that?! Did you fall for me?!
You were wonderful!
You jerks! Don't scare me like that!
That hurts.
You did great! You did just what I said!
You didn't do a thing.
Now that Team Straw Hat has won Round #2's Groggy Ring game,
they're allowed to swipe either a member of the Foxy Pirates' crew
or the Foxy Pirates' symbol!
Who does the Straw Hat captain want?!
Isn't it obvious?
Huh?! Is it me...?
They wanted me from the very start...!
Oh man... I'm not ready to go yet...
Crap it must be me! Our eyes just met...!
I bet it'll be me...
Could be me!
If he chooses me, I'll say goodbye to these guys with a smile...
They like me, I just know it...
Come on Luffy... Hurry...
Okay! I choose-
Hold on!
What is it, Nami?
Their boss will probably take part in the next round, right?
If we take Chopper back now but lose in this next round
they could just steal him again!
In which case taking their boss now
is the best way to get Chopper back and keep him.
U-U-Unbelievable! Is he going to call for the Foxy Pirates' captain?!
Th-That's the Peanut Strategy!
You guys are the lowest!
You lousy Peanutters!
Fight us fair and square!
There's no rule against it
but suddenly calling out an opponent's leader after the second round
is an obvious attempt at avoiding a fair-and-square head-on match!
I can't believe my ears! This is the devilish idea of an inhuman woman!
Her name is Nami the heathen navigator!
How dare you insult Nami-san?! I oughta filet you!
Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!
I hate them...
Even if it doesn't go against the rules,
it seems it would go against pirate ethics.
I'm with Nami on this!
Their reaction's only natural. You're in the wrong, Nami.
Will you shut up already?! Quit actin' cocky!
Our apologies!
Still, like it or not, Monkey D. Luffy, captain of the winning team
gets to decide how this game will unfold!
He's free to choose anyone he wants from Team Foxy!
He'll choose me I just know it...
It's obvious I'm the only choice here...
Is he gonna choose me? These guys are cool!
Say, Navigator.
Your proposal does give us an overwhelming advantage,
but that also makes their boss part of our crew.
No thanks.
Now that Team Straw Hat's harassment of our boss has ended,
it's time to pick someone!
Who will he choose?!
All right then. I wanna take back...
Chopper! Come back!
Oh no! Choppy!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Don't cry! You know we'd never lose!
Our boss has sunk into the ground from the weight of his feelings!
I can't believe they all rejected our boss like that!
Oh, Boss! It's okay! We need you!
We do, Boss!
G-Guys...
Let's teach these guys a lesson!
Yeah! I can't wait for the next round!
We love you, Boss!
Boss!
Guys...
Yes! You are my only true comrades!
Thank you!
Cut the crap will ya?
Boss!
I suggest you all ready yourselves!
What?! I'd never lose to you in a fight!
How many times must I repeat myself?
A fight and a game are two different things...
At last it's time for the final combat round!
First order of business:
establishing the battlefield!
The two competitors spin the cannon!
And then...
...wherever it stops will be where--!
Hold on! That was clearly not normal!
The battlefield has been set!
By sheer coincidence it's on the deck of our own Sexy Foxy!
Coincidence my butt! You idiot!
I'll now explain the rules of combat!
Everything within 50 meters of where the cannonball landed is part of the battlefield!
In other words, it's a 100-meter-wide circle!
Weapons are allowed as well as
anything else within the circle!
Only the two competitors are allowed inside the circle!
Knock your opponent out of the circle and you win! That's it!
Note that the air and water inside the circle still counts as in-bounds!
F! O! X! Y!
Foxy!
The Flower Cheerleaders are currently on the stage performing cheers for our boss,
while an opening fight is being held aboard the Foxy!
Additionally, the Association of Stalls is selling limited-edition Davy Back Fight merchandise
so be sure to check them out!
We don't need any of this! Just get started!
Note: "Foxy Pins"
...please!
Okay! Limited-edition Foxy pins!
Don't buy their junk!
Excuse me. Where's the participant...?
There! Just take him already!
What the hell?! Why does popcorn and a cola cost so much?!
If you don't like it, don't buy it.
Lower it 80%!
Get outta my face!
The boundaries are in place!
This ends the opening entertainment! Thank you for your patience!
Now for today's main event...
Combat! The bell will ring shortly!
Hurry to the spectator stands everyone!
What's happening?
The sky is turning dark...
This time we're being treated to a captain-versus-captain battle!
First, in the left figurehead corner...!
A man who takes on all challengers and boasts a legendary undefeated record
of 920 wins and 0 losses!
Our boss Silver Fox Foxy!
All right...
Listen up Luffy. You ain't your old self no more.
That hairstyle arouses a man's true wildness.
Some ask if the champion makes the afro or if the afro makes the champion...
Not even modern science can explain it.
Luffy... With an afro on, your punches will have some serious firepower.
Where's Straw Hat?!
Did he wimp out on us?!
And in the right corner hailing from East Blue!
The leader of a miniscule pirate band with a 100 million-Berry bounty...
..."Straw Hat" Monkey D. Luffy!
Wow! The afroed Luffy is all fired up in the right corner!
Lookin' sharp Luffy!
Are you kidding me?
Luffy looks so cool!
He certainly does.
Both fighters have stepped onto the battlefield!
Can Straw Hat successfully knock our boss out of the circle and protect his crew and pride?!
Or will our boss's legendary undefeated streak strip him of everything he has?!
This final and fateful combat round of the Davy Back Fight is about to begin!
What is all this?!
This is the dressing room.
It's a gloved fight, so choose anything you like.
Awesome!
Wow this is more like a costume room than a dressing room...
Look at all this stuff! And I can use anything I want Usopp!
Hey how about this? Does it look good?
No... This is it...
Hey Straw Hat! Nice fashion!
Your butt is as good as kicked!
Keep your arms tucked in and show 'im your golden right punch!
Yeah!
Whoa! His brotherly soul is burning red-hot!
Letting Usopp be his corner man was a mistake.
I wish he'd take this seriously...
I wouldn't act so confident if I were you, Champion!
He's liable to bite your head off! Better watch out!
All right, corner man! You're in the way! Scram!
Whoa! My job as corner man is over already?!
Corner man out!
Get goin' already!
You're absolutely right!
There's no need for me to remain here either! I'll leave as well!
What? The stands are...!
Oh cool! I didn't know they did that!
Now then, Straw Hat Luffy. Let's have some fun!
This entire ship is our battlefield! Rampage to your heart's desire!
We have plenty of skilled shipwrights, you see!
By sheer luck this bout is taking place aboard the Sexy Foxy!
What kind of deadly struggle is about to unfold?!
The two pirates are now all alone inside the spacious battlefield!
Boss!
Keep your undefeated streak going!
Win, Luffy! You hafta win!
His beam! Watch out for his beam!
Excitement fills the stands!
It's plunder or be plundered!
It's one match only with no time limit!
Silver Fox Foxy versus Straw Hat Luffy!
It's a head-to-head battle between these two pirate powerhouses!
The fate of everything hangs in the balance!
Here comes...
...the starting bell!
Let's do it!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Only my fist is slow!
You're not so tough! You're all show!
What?!
Come back!
Slow-Slow...
Oh no!
Just kidding!
Wha...?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Luffy!
He's floating! He's slow even when falling?
I told him to watch out for that!
Aww... Crap...
What's the matter Straw Hat? Ready to throw in the towel already?!
...what...?
Nine-Tails Rush!
Oh! Our boss unleashes a fierce attack right off the bat!
Straw Hat is helpless to do anything!
Huh? He isn't even budging...
No, that's not true!
The effects are slow too that's all!
That was just a little "hello."
The punches themselves didn't hurt you too much.
That much is obvious to me, rubber man!
Darn... it...
Well, your thirty seconds are about up!
It's hitting him all at once!
Oh no! He's going overboard!
Luffy!
Crap! The Slow-Slow Beam is more dangerous than I thought!
Beams sure are nice...
Guess I shouldn't stretch more than I need to...
Where'd that jerk go?!
Damn! I won't get hit by that anymore!
Come out, Split-Head!
Please don't take your anger out on the ears!
A-Another Slow-Slow?!
Welcome to my ship!
Why you...!
He got me!
Calm down, will you?
I'm trying to show you some hospitality here...
Those cannonballs have been Slow-Slow-ed...
If you can ride one then I can too!
Oh...! I wouldn't ride that one if I were you...
Oh, or that one.
Told you so!
Darn it...
Man he's wrecking his own ship...
I'm just getting started!
Slow-Slow Foxy Face Bombs!
Freaky!
Huh? Pin badges? They're bigger than the one I bought!
Of course we are! We're bombs!
You are?! Yikes!
Huh? A bomb just talked!
I'm... the real deal!
Sorry Straw Hat...
...but I upgraded my gloves!
And the Face Bombs' 30 seconds are just about up!
Oh yeah! Luffy! The body! The body!
Oh Usopp!
Hey, what's happening with the fight?
Dunno. Beats me.
Are you serious?!
E-Explosions suddenly rock our ship...
...which just happens to be the battlefield...
caused by Foxy Face Bombs that also happened to be loaded...!
Making their ship the battlefield is such a dirty trick!
Hey! Luffy! What's going on?!
Simmer down!
Using this to his advantage, our boss succeeded in blowing up Straw Hat Luffy with a cannon attack!
Is it all over for him?! He's nowhere to be seen!
Whew, that was close!
Indeed, it was a--!
What?!
Quit it! You're annoying!
Straw Hat Luffy is... alive!
Y-You serious?!
He's mind-boggling!
He somehow evaded the close-range cannon barrage!
What speed! I-Is this the true power of a man worth 100 million?!
Of course it is!
Just finish 'im already!
Oh! But it looks like our boss's next attack is already underway!
From out of the resulting smoke screen comes our boss's disturbing laughter!
But where exactly is he?!
What does "Silver Fox" Foxy have up his sleeve this time?!
There he is!
Okay, I hope you're ready!
You got blown up?!
I did not! Don't be stupid!
Liar!
Don't assume for one minute you'll leave this battlefield alive!
Slow-Slow Beam--!
Eh?!
Gum Hook!
No more beams for you! I'm gonna smash your arms!
He disappeared into the smoke again!
Huh?! There you are!
What? A board?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Now then! Which one is me? Where will the beam come from?!
Darn it! How should I know?! They all look like stupid-heads!
Stupid-heads...
There!
And you call yourself a warm-hearted individual?!
You're in for it now! Look up!
Huh?
Crap! A trap door!
That's what you get for being distracted!
You're the one who told me to look up!
You might wanna pay more attention!
Huh?
Wh-What the...?! Whoa! The floor's moving!
It's dragging me away!
There's Luffy!
Why'd he come out of there?!
Oh no! He'll lose if he falls into the water!
I ain't gonna fall in...!
So close!
Nah it'd be no fun if it ended so soon!
Hang in there, Straw Hat!
Geez! What's with this ship?!
Where'd you go, fox?!
What's this?!
A Foxy pin eerily taunts Straw Hat Luffy after his narrow escape!
In there!
The inside of the ship is our boss's playground! Will Luffy be lured in?!
No, Luffy! It's totally a trap!
He obviously has a bunch of booby traps set!
That jerk! I'm gonna beat his brains out!
Straw Hat Luffy rushes right in!
The battle has moved inside but I can't enter to give the play-by-play!
This is the true essence of this round:
a solitary battle between two combatants!
Get up! Get up Luffy! Remember your painful training!
Quit playin' around and sit down. I can't see.
Oh, a gun deck!
Man, it's big! I bet Usopp would love this!
Now, where is he?!
There he is!
All right! He's coming after me...!
Now he'll bust through the door at breakneck speed!
Little does he know...
...that this room is filled with spikes!
Now, rush in and get--
Oh. There he is.
Whoa what's with that room?
Who fires cannons inside other people's ships?! Seriously!
Oh. It's coming back.
You have some nerve! Are you trying to kill me?!
Dammit!
I'll show you!
Oh! He's running away!
"Infirmary"
Get back here!
Does this brat have any common sense?!
That's it! Foxy Face Transformation!
Stop right there, fox!
A person?
Dear me!
Whatever's the matter? Do you feel sick?
Where are you sick? The head? Are you sick in the head?
H-Huh?! Did anyone just come in here?
No I didn't see anyone. But never mind that...
What's wrong with you? Your face?
That's weird... I'm sure I saw him--
Hold on! That woman looked like him!
Could it be?!
Hey you! You're that guy's sister aren't you?!
Counter Fox Blow!
Fool!
What is this thing?!
That's weird! He really was in this room!
Is he even trying to fight?!
Oh! The kitchen!
Fish fish! Cut it up sour it up! Carpaccio!
Grill up a sole fa-mi-re-do!
Oh? Can I help you?
Have you seen a fox with its head split in two who looks like a real moron?!
That's going too far...!
It's you!
I was the lady in the infirmary too!
That thing too?!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Oh... no...
Nine-Tails Rush!
Don't think I lured you in here without a reason.
Go check out what's waiting for you when you get sent flying!
It ain't a living creature.
That'd be against the rules after all.
While a Slow-Slow Beam is in effect any impacts given are stored up and then go off all at once.
Go on now! Your life's final stop lies ahead!
30 seconds are up.
Huh? Where is he?
I'm... right here!
Feh-feh-feh-feh-feh!
And another feh!
I am Pilot Foxy! And...
...let me introduce you to the Gorilla Puncher 13!
A gorilla-like punching machine that's had every single flaw ironed out through constant improvement!
Is the gorilla face really necessary?!
Excellent point!
I mean shut up! Who asked you?!
Go, Gorilla Puncher 13!
How is it moving on its own?
It's a secret...!
You're sure sweatin' a lot...
Shut up!
You think you can dodge these measly punches don'tcha?
Slow-Slow Beam!
What? Where are you aiming--?
Take a look behind you!
Huh? Who's that?! A mirror?!
Yes! Mirrors reflect Slowmo Photons!
Got ya!
Ouch! Ouch!
Oh that hurt? Too hot for you?
I forgot to mention that this thing's punches are flaming hot!
Better watch out! Not even Sea Kings can withstand a beating from this!
Mirror Racket!
We're just getting started!
Slowpoke Ball Demon Coach! A two-sided attack with bouncing beams and punches!
Man, this is irritating! If I can just get close to him...!
Keep running! You'll end up squished between the gorilla and the mirror!
That's it!
I never thought of that!
What?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Got him!
Slow-Slow Beam! Beam! Beam!
Fool!
Gorilla Punch Golden Hits!
Round Three of this second Davy Back Fight, the combat round, is underway!
What's happening now is anyone's guess, but there's no doubt
a truly epic battle is taking place inside the ship!
Despite not being able to see him, the crowd cheers for our boss!
He ain't gonna lose!
Of course not! He's Luffy! And he has a 'fro!
Being Luffy is more than enough.
That damn fox...
What's so special about an afro?
Does it power you up or something?!
This is taking longer than usual...
Well, the guy is made of rubber.
He's made of rubber and has a 'fro!
Seriously, what's that have to do with anything?!
Oh my! There's activity on the deck!
Who has the upper hand?!
Or could the fight be over now?!
I see two figures!
Our boss is the one still standing!
Boss!
Meanwhile Straw Hat is charred black!
He seems to have taken some seriously heavy punches!
Luffy!
That's impossible...
How could some simple punches burn him?! What did he do?!
Look!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
Just when it seemed he was down for the count he got back up!
Looks like you barely pulled through, Straw Hat...
It's the brotherly soul! Afro power!
Kick his butt, Boss!
Take this!
This is the Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
I've restrained your arms and legs! But feel free to move anything else!
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
Rush!
30 seconds.
He's down for sure this time... No, wait!
Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy is up!
Whoa! Who is this guy?!
It's gotta be the 'fro! Is it the afro's wildness?!
Stubborn little...!
Take this!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Megaton Nine-Tails Rush!
Dammit, that's not fair! That beam's against the rules!
Usopp!
Whoa! This looks like the end...!
Dealing the punches ain't so easy either!
He's beating him to death out there!
Oh?! Again...?!
A-Again...?!
Luffy...!
I won't let you have...
...any of my crew mates...
...even if it costs me my life!
Luffy...
Straw... Straw Hat Luffy is on his feet once again!